<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Daniel Dewar Writing</title>
    <link>http://writing.daniel-dewar.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Daniel Dewar Writing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 09:48:52 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://writing.daniel-dewar.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The perfect description of blockchain technology — why it&#39;s becoming more simple</title>
      <link>http://writing.daniel-dewar.com/post/a-perfect-description-of-blockchain-technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2017 09:48:52 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://writing.daniel-dewar.com/post/a-perfect-description-of-blockchain-technology/</guid>
      <description>“Blockchain is a technology that allows natively digital transfer of value.”
 That line was buried in a Medium post by Karl Kreder, cofounder of Gridplus.io.
The more I read it the more I think it’s the best concise description of blockchain technology. The branding problem blockchain has always had is how to describe it in 25 words or less.
Not that being able to describe in such a limitation proves any value of what is being described, however it sure makes it easier to explain at networking events where you may need to offer a description over and over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Designing crypto tokens in light of the SEC announcement</title>
      <link>http://writing.daniel-dewar.com/post/designing-crypto-tokens-in-light-of-sec-announcement/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2017 09:48:52 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://writing.daniel-dewar.com/post/designing-crypto-tokens-in-light-of-sec-announcement/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this week the Securities and Exchange Commission handed down its ruling on crypto tokens as potential securities.
The investigation was prompted after the DAO “hack” that saw $55 million redirected by a rogue party in the DAO network.
In the specific instance of the DAO, the SEC found that the tokens were offered as securities, and therefore fell under regular securities laws. Applied to other tokens or ICOs, this would mean that coin offerings would be subject to SEC regulation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Founder Paralysis: An irrational (or rational) fear</title>
      <link>http://writing.daniel-dewar.com/post/founder-paralysis-a-moment-of-fear/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2017 09:48:52 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://writing.daniel-dewar.com/post/founder-paralysis-a-moment-of-fear/</guid>
      <description>Two days before I was due to fly to Liége to take part in the Wallifornia MusicTech Acceleration &amp;amp; Invest program, I was paralysed by an irrational—or rational—fear.
I was unable to get out of bed. For an extended time there was not enough energy or will to get up.
The night before I suffered through two terrible dreams.
The first was quite long but repetitive. I was meeting many people for the first time, and each time, they picked at me for not sharing more about myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sydney to Liége</title>
      <link>http://writing.daniel-dewar.com/post/sydney-to-liege/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 09:48:52 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://writing.daniel-dewar.com/post/sydney-to-liege/</guid>
      <description>Sydney Airport.
Abu Dhabi Airport.
Brussels Airport.
(wrong train)
Mechelen.
(turn around)
Eppegem.
Weerde.
Vilvoorde.
Schaerbeek.
Brussels-Nord.
Brussels Airport.
(right train)
Leuven.
Liége-Guillemins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A First-Time Founder&#39;s Notes on Finding the Ideal Co-Founder</title>
      <link>http://writing.daniel-dewar.com/post/finding-the-ideal-co-founder/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 09:48:52 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://writing.daniel-dewar.com/post/finding-the-ideal-co-founder/</guid>
      <description>I can only say I feel extremely lucky in finding Paperchain&amp;rsquo;s co-founder, Rahul.
I started fleshing out the idea for Paperchain in July 2016. All I had was knowledge of the problem—and as I&amp;rsquo;ve learned further, inadequate knowledge of the problem—and an idea on how it could be solved.
That was the genesis of Paperchain. I knew the industry had trouble identifying rights owners and I knew disparate databases was a driving cause.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Recommended Reading List for Founders</title>
      <link>http://writing.daniel-dewar.com/post/founder-recommended-reading-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2017 09:48:52 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://writing.daniel-dewar.com/post/founder-recommended-reading-list/</guid>
      <description>The list below are titles that have been invaluable to my growth as a founder. They are mostly fictional.
They are not books that will teach you sales frameworks, iteration methodology or operational structures.
These are books that have shaped the foundation of my understanding of the world, which becomes the core of how I value my business and my involvement in it.
They are works that evoke the soul of the world and its peoples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Very Easy Death</title>
      <link>http://writing.daniel-dewar.com/post/a-very-easy-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 02:12:05 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://writing.daniel-dewar.com/post/a-very-easy-death/</guid>
      <description>There is no such thing as a natural death: nothing that happens to a man is ever natural, since his presence calls the world into question. All men must die: but for every man his death is an accident and, even if he knows it and consents to it, an unjustifiable violation.
 I have thought about death for as long as I can remember. Not dying. Death. I have no desire to die although one day I will.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>