<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Daniel Dewar Writing</title>
    <link>http://writing.daniel-dewar.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Daniel Dewar Writing</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 09:48:52 +1000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://writing.daniel-dewar.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Sydney to Liége</title>
      <link>http://writing.daniel-dewar.com/post/sydney-to-liege/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2017 09:48:52 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://writing.daniel-dewar.com/post/sydney-to-liege/</guid>
      <description>Sydney Airport.
Abu Dhabi Airport.
Brussels Airport.
(wrong train)
Mechelen.
(turn around)
Eppegem.
Weerde.
Vilvoorde.
Schaerbeek.
Brussels-Nord.
Brussels Airport.
(right train)
Leuven.
Liége-Guillemins.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A First-Time Founder&#39;s Notes on Finding the Ideal Co-Founder</title>
      <link>http://writing.daniel-dewar.com/post/finding-the-ideal-co-founder/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2017 09:48:52 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://writing.daniel-dewar.com/post/finding-the-ideal-co-founder/</guid>
      <description>I can only say I feel extremely lucky in finding Paperchain&amp;rsquo;s co-founder, Rahul.
I started fleshing out the idea for Paperchain in July 2016. All I had was knowledge of the problem—and as I&amp;rsquo;ve learned further, inadequate knowledge of the problem—and an idea on how it could be solved.
That was the genesis of Paperchain. I knew the industry had trouble identifying rights owners and I knew disparate databases was a driving cause.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Recommended Reading List for Founders</title>
      <link>http://writing.daniel-dewar.com/post/founder-recommended-reading-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2017 09:48:52 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://writing.daniel-dewar.com/post/founder-recommended-reading-list/</guid>
      <description>The list below are titles that have been invaluable to my growth as a founder. They are mostly fictional.
They are not books that will teach you sales frameworks, iteration methodology or operational structures.
These are books that have shaped the foundation of my understanding of the world, which becomes the core of how I value my business and my involvement in it.
They are works that evoke the soul of the world and its peoples.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Very Easy Death</title>
      <link>http://writing.daniel-dewar.com/post/a-very-easy-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 May 2017 02:12:05 +1000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://writing.daniel-dewar.com/post/a-very-easy-death/</guid>
      <description>There is no such thing as a natural death: nothing that happens to a man is ever natural, since his presence calls the world into question. All men must die: but for every man his death is an accident and, even if he knows it and consents to it, an unjustifiable violation.
 I have thought about death for as long as I can remember. Not dying. Death. I have no desire to die although one day I will.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>